<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Learn Piano</string>
    <string name="main_title">Lets learn to play</string>
    <string name="sub_title">Piano</string>
    <string name="chord_image_desc">Chord Image</string>
    <string name="prev_chord">Previous Chord</string>
    <string name="next_chord">Next Chord</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>

    <string-array name="chord_titles">
        <item>A Major Chord</item>
        <item>A # Major Chord</item>
        <item>B Major Chord</item>
        <item>B # Major Chord</item>
        <item>C Major Chord</item>
        <item>C # Major Chord</item>
        <item>D Major Chord</item>
        <item>D # Major Chord</item>
        <item>E Major Chord</item>
        <item>E # Major Chord</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="chord_descriptions">
        <item>Place your thumb on the A key (white key).\n\n
Place your middle finger on the C# key (black key two keys to the right of A).\n\n
Place your pinky on the E key (white key next to C#).</item>
        <item>Place your right thumb on A# (A sharp), which is the black key to the right of A.\n\n
Place your middle finger on C# (C sharp), which is the black key to the right of C.\n\n
Place your pinky finger on F (F natural), which is the white key to the right of E.</item>
        <item>Place your right thumb on B, which is the white key two keys to the left of middle C.\n\n
Place your middle finger on D#, which is the black key to the right of D.\n\n
Place your pinky finger on F#, which is the white key to the right of F.</item>
        <item>Place your right thumb on B#, which is the white key three keys to the left of middle C.\n\n
Place your middle finger on D## (double sharp), which is the black key to the right of D#.\n\n
Place your pinky finger on F## (double sharp), which is the white key to the right of F#.</item>
        <item>Place your thumb on C, which is the white key to the left of the group of two black keys (C# and D#).\n\n
Place your index finger on E, which is the white key to the right of D.\n\n
Place your ring finger on G, which is the white key to the right of F.</item>
        <item>Place your thumb on C#, which is the black key to the right of C.\n\n
Place your index finger on F, which is the white key to the right of E.\n\n
Place your ring finger on G#, which is the black key to the right of G.</item>
        <item>Place your thumb on D, which is the white key to the left of the group of two black keys (D# and E#).\n\n
Place your index finger on F#, which is the white key to the right of E.\n\n
Place your ring finger on A, which is the white key to the right of G.</item>
        <item>Place your thumb on D#, which is the black key to the right of D.\n\n
Place your index finger on G, which is the white key to the right of F.\n\n
Place your ring finger on A#, which is the black key to the right of A.</item>
        <item>Place your thumb on E, which is the white key to the left of the group of two black keys (E# and F##).\n\n
Place your index finger on G#, which is the black key to the right of G.\n\n
Place your ring finger on B, which is the white key to the right of A#.</item>
        <item>Place your thumb on F, which is the white key to the left of the group of two black keys (F# and G#).\n\n
Place your index finger on A, which is the white key to the right of G.\n\n
Place your ring finger on C, which is the white key to the right of B.</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
